Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/subiditadas-916083154 (LinkedIn)

Top Skills

Sourcing
Screening Resumes
Technical Recruiting

Languages

Hindi

English

Assamese

Certifications

Tech Recruitment Certified Professional Accessibility in Action

Subidita Das

Technical Recruiter at Microsoft Bengaluru

Summary

Subidita is having 3+ years of experience in scouting the very best talent available in the market currently operating in India. She is approachable and open minded recruiter who believe in trustworthy and fulfilling relationship with the clients and candidates. She is always a good listener and mapper who understand the demands of both the parties and source according to that.

Her primary point of view is "right job and right fit" .

If you are a technological geek having a streamline experience in product, cloud, enterprise, eCommerce or Internet background feel free to reach her out for something exciting for your career.

She will always be available on v-sdas@microsoft.com

Hiring specialities-: Dotnet/Azure IAAS/Skype for Business/Windows system administrator/Onedrive and Sharepoint/Java/C++/C#/Python/R/KDB/Quant/Devops/Application Support/QA

Experience

Microsoft Technical Recruiter January 2020 - Present (8 months) Bangalore

CareerNet Technologies

2 years 7 months

Consultant

April 2019 - December 2019 (9 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Involved in end to end recruitment and handling

- 1. Digital, Social and Portal sourcing
- 2. Taking care of market mapping with req. specific demand

- 3. Working on vanilla and niche skills
- 4. Working on maintaining SLA and TAT.

Associate Consultant

June 2017 - March 2019 (1 year 10 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Involved in end to end recruitment from

- 1. Analysing the JD
- 2. Sourcing plan activities
- 3. Market Mapping
- 4. Screening
- 5. Scheduling
- 6. Pre and Post interview follow up

Myntra Jabong HR Intern May 2016 - July 2016 (3 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Study of "Engaging Gen Z @ CC Myntra".

Research on employee engagement of past, present and future

Analysing the activities that engages employees on and off work

Retrieving the data and computing it for future forecast with TAT

Understanding the quality of engagement and beneficial for the employees

Lifetrenz

Internship

December 2015 - February 2016 (3 months)

Bengaluru Area, India

Product marketing and solution branding

Involved into product marketing in the domestic market viable to B2B Solution branding of the app in accordance of the customers Strategic implementation of the product to channelise the solution for the customers and vendors

Indian Oil Corporation Limited Summer Internship June 2013 - July 2013 (2 months)

Guwahati Area, India

Summer Trainee and basic field of training was on components required for producing Crude Oil and major products- LPG, Motor spirit(Petrol), Aviation turbine fuel, Kerosene, High speed diesel, Light diesel oil, Raw petroleum coke.

The working of the process and the parts which are implemented for the plant was described practically.

Education

Mats Institute Of Management and Entrepreneurship, Bangalore Master of Business Administration - MBA, Human Resources Management and Services · (2015 - 2017)

Royal School of engineering & Technology, Assam

Bachelor of Engineering - BE, Mechanical Engineering · (2010 - 2014)